If you can't trust your mind, trust your heart.
Words on Bathroom Walls is a drama, romance film directed by Thor Freudenthal.
Diagnosed with a mental illness halfway through his senior year of high school, a witty, introspective teen struggles to keep it a secret
while falling in love with a brilliant classmate who inspires him to open his heart and not be defined by his condition.
Adam, played by Charlie Plummer.
Beth, played by Molly Parker.
Paul, played by Walton Goggins.
Father Patrick, played by Andy Garcia.
Maya, played by Taylor Russell.
Rebecca, played by AnnaSophia Robb.
Words on Bathroom Walls is a 2020 American coming-of-age romantic drama film directed by Thor
Freudenthal and written by Nick Naveda, based on the novel of the same name by Julia Walton.
The film stars Charlie Plummer, Andy García, Taylor Russell,
AnnaSophia Robb, Beth Grant, Molly Parker and Walton Goggins.
Words on Bathroom Walls was released on August 21, 2020, by
Roadside Attractions and LD Entertainment.
The film explores themes of high school,
schizophrenia, narration, cooking, melancholy.
The tone is uplifting and emotional.